Learning CapCut day 25. Today, we will
learn how to create this type of trend
neon effect transition the two in very
simple steps.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Duplicate the clip and move it down. Cut
the clip from the middle. Go to effects
and select [music] neon outline. Go to
object and select overlay. Duplicate the
effect and [music] apply it to the next
clip. Go to object and select overlay.
Go to mask and select [music]
horizontal. Rotate it to minus 90°. Go
to mask again, select horizontal and
rotate [music] it to 90°. Add one
keyframe at the start and another at the
end. Go to splice and set it to 0%.
[music] Apply the same steps to the next
clip. Thanks for watching.